what's up guys welcome back to another
set and figure out podcast so i think
we're on episode like 22 23 something
like that and it's gonna be a little
different podcast so we have a returning
guest mr mr roy and then we have mr q
what it do guys so appreciate you guys
will you guys i bet i'm laughing bro i'm
just looking at you bro leave me alone
so i told i told alex not to mention my
arm during the podcast and he just wants
to cyber bully me
just for you guys so i hope you guys
enjoyed this so what's up yo what's up
cute good having you here good to be
here bro i'm saying last time we chopped
it up was at that fx summit shout out to
the summit if everyone was there but now
it's good to be here bro i i'm in miami
this weekend i was throwing with
destroying and just in the fort
lauderdale area so it's dope to pull up
bro yeah i know you're mr viral now so i
don't know i'm not i'm honored to have
you here
you know what i'm saying we just all
keep working so like so let's talk about
that real quick like bro what why would
you do you went viral yeah i mean a
couple things bro like i know what it's
like to go viral and be the main actor
like in the you know the main person in
the video and also know what it's like
to make content that doesn't include me
that also goes viral so like you know
the one that i was in i i smoked a joint
in game
in a professional league after a
touchdown and you know it did millions
and millions of views and i did it for a
bigger reason you know i got cut from
that league but i understood that if i'm
gonna make the conversation be had then
somebody has to be willing to be the
scapegoat you know somebody has to be
willing to do it on a level like that
and after i hit the gas i had like three
four more touchdowns
one mvp and just made the statement like
you know athletes can still smoke
cannabis and be high-level thinkers and
high-level performers and somebody had
to do it so
and then outside of that in the last 20
days on my instagram i've been creating
reels and things of that nature that
they don't include me but it's still
creative director more so content and
it's done over 50 million views in the
last 20 days so oh fire yeah it's just
you know like like i said bro we have
many skills we're much more than traders
so it's fun to like
you know see yeah just live life because
you don't care to get kicked out of the
league you just you're just doing your
thing i mean that's not the reason of
what we do is like the freedom bro like
we all wanted to escape somebody telling
us you got to be here at this time
you're going to make this set amount of
money like the market is uncapped our
time is free we choose what we do with
our time so it literally was the per you
know the stars had to align for me to
join a league and say
i've already been trading for six five
six years this league is just something
i'm doing for fun like how j cole
winning played basketball everyone's
like j cole why are you gonna play
basketball i saw that it's like because
there's going to come a time where i
physically do not have the option of
choice so for me it was like i knew the
charts weren't going anywhere i knew i
could trade when the season was over so
i devoted three months of my life to
getting back into playing football just
to do that you know just to hit the gas
just to go viral [__] it i mean yeah i
mean
i was watching the league like a year
and a half ago and i was saying to
myself like i saw they had a celebration
cam and i thought that was really cool
and unique and that's when i had the
idea like damn what if someone scored a
touchdown and went and sparked the gas
like
and so i was very methodical about not
doing it the first game like the first
game i could have done it and got kicked
out then but i waited till like the
sixth or seventh game of the season
because i wanted to show people i could
perform at a high level before doing
something like that and then when i did
it i didn't wait till the end of the
game i did it the third play of the game
i threw a touchdown that's crazy hit the
gas and then proceeded to cook [__]
while cooked so i was like
but you've been playing balls since
before yeah yeah you've been playing
ball yeah i've been coming talking about
the story talking about yeah i mean yeah
i've been playing since high school uh
me and my boy probably went to the same
high school shout out to hayfield and
northern virginia
and i didn't have any offers bro like so
the biggest thing is trying to get a
scholarship to get free education i
didn't have anything so i went to junior
college in the middle of nowhere kansas
i was betting on myself bro that's why
all of us have reached the levels we've
reached because we bet on ourselves and
i was willing to do that and i ended up
becoming the number one quarterback in
the nation i had a bunch of full-ride
scholarships to all these different
schools i chose the university of
memphis i get to memphis and my roommate
ends up being this six foot seven 240
pound guy who ended up going first round
as well so i sat behind him and that was
a lesson in season of like strip away
you know the the ego and strip away any
type of feeling of like why am i not
getting the shine and learn to be a team
player learn to be supportive even if
it's the moment is not for you so
you know after
sitting behind him and then moving to
denver my my best friend my roommate he
became a millionaire bro his first
contract was nine million dollars but i
was working at target for playing ball
for playing ball bro he he got dropped
into the denver broncos he asked me to
come live with him i move out there i'm
like this is lit bro my best friend is
making millions but i didn't have a car
i only had like two 3k to my name but i
always made it very clear i was like bro
i don't ever want you to give me money
like i don't want that to be a thing
that comes between us our friendship
needs more to me than you just giving me
a couple g's and so that's what caused
me to get into trading bro like i was i
was stocking shelves at target 2 a.m to
10 a.m for three four months started
googling ways to make money online i see
the word forex i think it stands for
fake rolex
right
nothing to do with it
but after enough conversations i always
ask myself if not this then what i
actually wanted to get into real estate
but without a car to go see the
properties yeah i'm like this is the
only thing i can do for my phone or
laptop that's gonna actually give me the
results that i want and that was the
beginning bro yeah that's crazy like
another forks like like queue yeah
that's pretty crazy relax so that i know
you posted a video on your instagram
once that you were walking yeah walking
like next to like uh against the traffic
i think it was like it's like like on
the highway or something and you were
literally like you look younger yeah
look now so i got into trading june 26
2017. that video was like march 28th
2018. so like a year interest rate so
like a year some change i'm still not
seeing results i would have like a
couple decent days and think i had it
figured out and then account blown and
it's like but the conviction that's why
i tell people like sight is a function
of the eyes vision is a function of the
heart so that video was my vision like
that was me understanding that even
though right now in this current moment
although i have three dollars i know
these are seven figure feet and like the
fact that i'm walking against traffic is
just the symbolism of we're going
against the norm like i have my bags i
have no money i get everyone that's in
in their cars probably coming from a
nine to five but i gotta walk to the
airport because i invested everything i
have to go to this convention to learn
and gain more wisdom and that's why i
realized i was always willing to go back
to zero just to get a little bit more
gain because i knew the game was the
only thing separating me from the
results that other people had that's
crazy bro that's that's a story bro
seeing things like that like i love it
you got me seeing how q back in target
james homeless in his like basement
basically donuts i got dunkin donuts sir
but like one thing is like i mean
because it's kind of crazy because we
were all well you definitely started
before me but we were kind of all like
in the trenches at the same time you get
me and now where we are now obviously
which we're all blessed and it's great
but what it kind of like like gives me
like goosebumps says same way how at
those times we were in the trenches and
then we came out there's guys right now
either watching this or like going to
watch in the future that they're in the
trenches right now you know like two or
three years and then they're going to
come out you got me that's what's crazy
to me because anybody could just come
out whenever you just gotta hit like
consistency that's what a lot of people
feel like they lack but you know only
the strong are gonna make it out you
just gotta really want it but i mean if
i can pick both of you guys brains that
person that's watching that's trying to
make that breakout obviously looking at
it from this side you understand what
you were doing wrong at that time how
how much you were stressing over trading
and how much that was impacting you what
do you guys feel like was that shift
from target and from duncan to be able
to actually get consistent with trading
or to make that part of your lifestyle i
mean he said it there's like no other
way out like it's either that or that
like this there's literally no other
result all you had was three bucks
you're about back yeah i mean i like how
was my job at the time probably had a
little bit more because then i had
another business um but there's no other
option it's that or it's just gotta
happen i'm gonna just keep failing until
it happens in my opinion you gave me
that i feel that's what kept me going
and then something that like i never
lost hope was seeing you know all the
other guys on social media you know like
making it happen i'm like brothers it's
legit you gave me like it could really
go down
for sure i think the biggest thing was
just like i feel like even with your
podcast bro you decided you want to do a
podcast and now you have enough
equipment for like seven podcasts yeah
it's the mindset though of like once you
put your mind to this making that
decision that concrete decision then
it's like it doesn't matter what
obstacles come in the way like you said
the first episode you guys did you said
the the microphone was back it was a
mission and people were upset that they
couldn't hear roy they thought he was
underwater with squidward i hope you
guys are happy now i hope you guys can
hear me loud and clear
well for those of you guys that don't
know we filmed that podcast three times
like shout out to roy because my first
time ever being on a podcast was on
roy's uh channel on um
and to me it was like i can't believe i
can't like make this happen the first
time you get me the first time something
happened with the camera and record and
roy isn't from miami so he was like you
were flying out
for the whole summit that was going on
like you were like in the mission back
and forth and roy was stressed already
just for the summit alone so having him
come back in like two three times was
like my bad i'm like bro did you forget
to hit record like does the camera not
have an sd card no but i appreciate you
having me on the podcast and what i like
about you guys stories honestly it's
pretty similar it's a story of not
giving up because everybody who's
watching this is probably in a period
where they've had success and they've
come back down and they can see
themselves being successful but they
don't know how to get there what i'm
always trying to do is kind of reach
those individuals and bridge that gap
between what they have to do today
like what is it what are some things
that you guys were doing at that time on
a day-to-day basis you're tired from
work you get home what are some things
that you guys are doing that you feel
like set you apart from the from the
pack yeah i mean what i love so much
even like playing professional football
and even college football is like every
single practice would be specifically
scheduled like every 30 minutes you know
exactly what it was scheduled for and
they were very particular about making
sure within those 30 minutes to an hour
that we maximized those intervals so i'm
like we got a three hour practice there
was sometimes be 15 minutes broken down
within that three hours and it just made
me realize and be more aware of like
even as an entrepreneur at home if i'm
this diligent about what i do with my
time if i start blocking my hours and
saying i gotta show up and try to give
these blocks my best my all no different
than when i'm at practice then that's
where people will see results i think
people get caught up in being busy
versus productive and it's like okay
yeah i was working from 8 am to 8 pm
whereas like i could work from 9 00 a.m
to noon but if i don't have my phone on
and i'm super locked in and just you
know what i'm saying really being
productive then it's you're getting more
done so that's that yeah that's pretty
interesting you say that because like
now like me and me and my i have i have
a couple partners on different
businesses and like we we're like
figuring out right now that exactly we
said the the structuring hour per blocks
like i'm getting to the point now where
like i'll structure like my bathroom
breaks like i won't go to the bathroom
unless like i got to get me and that way
your day is so much more sufficient you
get personally i like getting everything
done in the morning get everything out
in the morning and then i like leaving
at least two three hours throughout the
day which is creative space so like
lately like now i've been getting into
like this new mindset where i'm just
trying to like build new [__] or just
make [__] happen right so i literally
get my phone
i've tried to leave it at the house but
i literally can't leave at the house you
never know a phone call just pops up but
i leave my phone in the like in the
office and i go to the other room and i
just think tv off no music bro i'm just
looking outside and i'm just thinking of
some [__] because you got to give like
that free time to like structure
creative stuff but that comes with
building those blocks that's crazy they
see that you had that back in the day i
didn't figure that out to like recently
yeah i mean because
the same way we're like very
conservative about how we spend our
money and i talked to people about this
all the time it's like we spend our
money we can always make the money back
but we spend the time we can't make the
time back yeah so like if we're going to
be stingy about our money we need to be
10x stingy about our time bro
because at least the bread we can get
back on the back end like the time we
don't get that back bro so like i'm
hella stingy about my time where i go
who even phone calls i used to find
myself being on on the phone with people
for 30 40 minutes and i got to a point
where i realized like
as much as i could just continue to
shoot the [__] with this person for 40
minutes if we're not talking about
anything like i gotta go bro like if i'm
in a season of elevation or season like
sometimes we gotta separate sometimes it
takes that bro because sometimes people
are so close to you in relation that
it's hard for them to be able to
understand that separation in order for
you to reach that elevation and honestly
bro when my when my uh my amygdala and
my hippocampus are activating on on all
cylinders
i'm tough to outwork i'm tough to beat
what is that what is that exactly the
hippocampus i don't know what that is
it's a certain area of your brain i've
been i've been putting roy on to
understand even the brain is 80 water so
it's like even staying hydrated and
making sure that people incorporate that
on their day to day why because he's
he's he's a non-believer
oh it's a funny word
talking about elevation yeah i know
you've hit six figure days yeah gangster
congratulations hold on hold on sorry
talk about elevation talk to us about
level up before this looks bigger again
let's talk about level up jason's talked
about his six figure days we're not
getting into this you know but talk to
us about level up i mean so level up is
something that ro and i basically
created so like one thing is having the
society like you know like having like
the community having everybody like you
educate them but like it sucks you get
me not having the money when you had
three dollars in the bank went i mean
the way that the reason why i'm
profitable is thank to a funding company
because if i didn't get that big payout
it would set me aside to take less
amount of trades so once i got that big
payout i understood that all right
though now i got 12 months of my monthly
expenses covered but i literally i don't
got to do [__] i can really go [__] off
for a year kind of how james did for
like six months he [__] up in the
middle of europe like whatever he did
but i can just do nothing and i'm still
got my whole interior paid for so like
mira you know talked about it chopped it
up and then we you know we got the right
partners the right investors and we
literally created a leveled up society
where we fund people and then along the
side with that since we educate people
we literally teach them how to get
funded there's many funding companies
out there which they we all offer you
know more or less the same thing
parameters kind of change a little bit
but we what we offer is a society like
we don't want to just free to get funded
like we want you to grow along with the
business we want a new lamboro to come
out a new cube be a new you know alex g
or anybody to come out you gave me
traders are popping up all the time
shows you that anything is possible
that's kind of where what we created
okay
i just wanted to
know a little bit more about that i
appreciate it as long as people
understand too how like young this like
like we are a part of the gold rush as
far as trading is concerned 100 and but
that's as long as people understand too
the same way not everyone struck gold
it's like not everyone's going to hit
this level of trading that's facts bro i
mean not everyone wants to hear but i'm
gonna be honest the same way not
everyone will hit that level of real
estate and not everyone will hit that
level of drop shipping okay okay but say
that again the goal because like i i
think people are going to overlook that
say it again because that means perfect
yes it's just it's just the numbers are
the numbers bro like for me when they
said hey jason out of high school just
to let you know 0.01 percent get a
division one full ride scholarship i
heard that statistic and i had two
choices i could either be so
frightened by
trying to climb that hill
that i just said all right [__] it i'm
gonna go to the military or i'm gonna
walk on somewhere and see what happens
or i could double down bet on myself go
juco play with two separated shoulders
and become the number one quarterback in
the nation because i tell people all the
time it's like what you practice in the
dark will get praised in the light
and so if people are actually back
testing at home if people actually
taking their demos serious if people
actually working to get funded or even
trading their own capital it's really
two choices like you can trade your own
bread and be a little bit more
aggressive you might not you know what i
mean you might not it's gonna it's gonna
be a lot riskier it's gonna be a lot
edgier style of trading or you can go
the funded route and try to do your best
to maintain a conservative style of
trading so that we can pass your
challenges get paid out periodically and
as long as people focus on tomorrow
coming then it's like there's no reason
of risking it all today
right it's like you plan on waking up
tomorrow yes or yes
okay perfect now that we got that out
the way why are you risking your entire
account today
and this usually stems from comparison
teddy roosevelt said comparison is a
thief of joy so it's like if i'm
constantly looking at what someone else
is doing what's that gonna do that's
gonna try to cause me to rush my process
for sure because you get fomo a lot of
people see everybody's journey and
they'll they want the pro they want the
results now but they don't understand
how long it took cause like none of us
were sitting there putting up vlogs when
we were eating [__] and [__] blowing
accounts like nobody wants to see me
blow three us 30 accounts but after you
get that [__] down then everybody wants
to pay attention so after a while
everybody wants the results right now
with the funded programs is there any
advice that you guys would give my
advice for people is kind of what you
guys were saying which is don't rush
your process versus someone else's it
might take you a couple tries it might
take you a few tries as long as you're
still consistently heading towards that
right direction you're going to get it
eventually
at chart addicts we coach a bunch of
students it might take somebody five or
six times
on their try but then they can become
success successful and have a consistent
four or five months on a program and so
really it's about the consistency
jason said about self-belief at the
beginning and so what are you guys
biggest uh pointers for those funded
challenges and what people should be
paying attention to i mean at the end of
the day like just having a plan like i
said you know there's there's really
only two ways to build an account you
either go with a bigger account size
whether you do funded account or whether
you try to work out a deal with someone
to do some type of capital management
it's just people need to understand
opm's as well other people's money like
if you don't have the money but you gain
the skill set and you have enough
backing whether it's an fx book or
previous trading history so then go to
an investor and say hey i have a skill
set and if you're willing to bet on me
let me apply that skill set to your
capital like it's you know it's
i'm all about skill sets at the end of
the day whether it's playing football
whether it's public speaking whether
it's adobe photoshop premiere
like it doesn't matter bro like it's
just the skill sets i view this [__]
like a nba 2k character and i want to
get all my attributes to 99 not because
of anyone else but because it's like if
i feel like i have the op and a ceiling
and a potential to do that why wouldn't
i like that's the the beauty of the
pursuit of all of this you know so
trading is just one aspect bro like i
got i got so many other things i'm way
more passionate about than trading i
gained my passion for trading through
just being in it every day i feel i feel
like a lot of people lose sight of that
because they they want to get all the
passion for like for me trading is cool
but it's probably like now consumes like
35 of my day you get me like i don't
like trading is cool don't get me wrong
it's there it's not going anywhere and
me as much passionate as i grow for it
it's not going to grow for me like it's
just going to grow with me over time so
now my new passion is just building
getting involved in other things because
i could manage that for example let's
just say i don't know i i make cups
right let's say all the money i'm making
forex i invest i reinvest into cups all
right there i can run ads make new
designs and cups do brand deals make
them [__] look crazy and [__] you
know but that i could be passionate for
because what i put towards the cup is
going to give it back to me bro i can
like
do anything i want in front of these
charts they're not doing nothing for me
you get me and like i kind of learned
that over time but you know a lot of
people cannot find that error because
they come in only having passion for
trading but over time the markets will
humble you to that point to your point
that you're saying about how to get like
funded easier
but we literally have a minimum trading
days for a reason
people want to pass on one day like what
you say people are we waking up tomorrow
yes or yes okay so we we literally set
you guys up to succeed we set a minimum
trading days for a reason because we
don't want you to come in no minimum on
trading days because then boom you want
to pass first second day that's not
ideal because now you're rushing it we
give you 10 minimum trading digits so
you're broke guys take your time like
there's no need to rush if you rush if
you pass before then all right cool but
just know that we don't want you to pass
right away we give you 30 days 45 days
whatever the case is that we give you
but we give you a minimum to know that
you guys there's no rush i tell
everybody if you're looking to target 10
a month go for 2.5 a week times 4 10 a
month if you can get one trade a week
for 2.5 a week just take a break come
back to the charts because the markets
will give you an opportunity like that
week and you guys you guys can't see
this off camera but he has it written on
his trading computer it says two and a
half percent a week equals ten percent a
month yeah right there so it's serious
and that's been there for like
like a year and a half two years for
sure i want to ask you about that though
because you know obviously people people
know i have my affirmations on the back
of my phone i've been doing like for
like last three four years so i want you
to kind of give your reasoning behind
like why do you have things visual for
you to see what you know the 2.5 a week
to set and forget
why is it important for it to be
something you see every day well i mean
for me it's like
you get very you get very distracted you
know social media life you know
relationship drama whatever you got
going there's a lot of distractions so
like i personally don't like training
for my phone like i usually do it at my
computer i set an alarm set and forget
so whenever i'm trading in front of the
computer like i need to literally remind
myself you know how many times that [__]
has helped me where i'm like i'm about
to close a trade no set up for it's not
on my take profit and the trades paid
out yeah there's times where it takes me
out of break even [__] happens but to me
this is like like you guys right now are
in like my den this is like this is like
mine
it's like my zone yeah yeah i appreciate
you letting us know because you know how
treasured my shirt is too so it's like
to let anyone in no but i have to set up
for like people to come in and feel at
home too you got me but to your question
like like i come here to work to trade
so everything that i have there's to
remind me of basically i have filtered
everything out to a cone to the most
important
and that's it everything else i don't i
don't need to remember there we go i
mean this this podcast is called set and
forget i do want to talk to you guys
both one thing i admire about both of
you is you guys are both kind of swing
traders yeah you're both very patient
for the setup and patient for it to play
out once you're in
for me personally i'm a scalper a very
different personality and i really don't
like to stay in the markets that long
what do you guys think is the difference
is it a personality thing i know you and
i talked about it on the podcast with
raul whether it was personality versus
just preference
i kind of want to get your take jason
you think his personality or preference
you you and your brother are planning on
doing some real estate deals depending
on when you get in it could be months or
years before you end up getting out
what's the difference in trading i get
into a deal with your usd it could be
weeks it could be months before i decide
to get out of the deal because i'm happy
with the exit price so it's not so much
uh
you know is it trading style it's it's
all in your head bro everything
everything is is in our minds it's all
the same crypto i have a different exit
strategy i'm planning on buying and
holding for three to five years that's
my buried treasure it's like everything
i'm putting in there it might as well
not exist and i also do that for like
for my own internal pressure to keep my
foot on the gas because like i've
learned about myself if i leave too much
money in my bank account then i get very
comfortable i get very relaxed i get
very
nonchalant it's like i have way too many
goals and things that i had to put my
own internal pressure on and it's like
when you start burying that treasure and
only leave yourself with a set amount to
pull from that forces you to get up
every single day and hunt as if you had
[__] nothing
there we go that's crazy do you have any
crypto yeah i mean you know it's it's
like i have xrp i have to coin i have
xdc i mean i have a good amount also
shout out to happy dad our sponsor shout
out to the boys full center all around
for the boys i don't even drink beer
well i mean
where's the sponsor i didn't get no
sponsors
no no but it's on the way
podcast we talked about nfts and crypto
did you guys getting deeper into the
game i know that
even when we spoke the crypto markets
were still down yeah you were kind of
feeling that pressure are you still in
that game oh are you no longer in that
game if i was feeling the pressure back
then i'm i'm like knocked out of sleep
right now like i'm i'm like then we were
talking i was probably down like 65 70
now i'm probably in like 99.999
i invested into four altcoins that i
bought let's just say at a dollar
they're at point zero zero zero zero
zero one right now and i'm down over six
figures in in in all coins now when you
were when you were looking for those
projects was it something that you like
research and believed in or was it just
something that you sort of saw potential
in how did you kind of do that process
amazing question i'm glad i asked i'm
glad you asked that
i closed my eyes when i picked the wrong
very glad yeah so i so i give my
experience and my advice to the guys out
there like
yo roy you gotta buy this [__] right now
bro you're just probably this is gonna
go crazy and yeah that's that's that's
how you bought it yeah that's what
happened so you guys if your uber driver
is telling you to buy dogecoin just get
out the uber yes and don't do it no no
bro literally i that was the week that i
made 70 or like 67k and one like one
trade
all of that money went into uh like all
these altcoins this guy just convinced
the [__] out of me bro whatever he got
me obviously he didn't make no money off
of it or at least i don't think he owns
the coins which i highly doubt it but
like he was the way he was explaining to
me was he was so passionate about it
it's like bro because this is when like
the metaverse nfts when everything was
like bro like we're going to start
living in these vr's you get me that's
right i'm trying to look like at an
all-time high yeah
bro like imagine the highest point yeah
that's that's where your boy got it i
mean i'll say this bro like with any
crypto or any investment period it's
just all draw down until you decide to
actually liquidate your loss so it's
like
as long as you're not liquidating then
[__] sit in the dd for the next three
to five years and you'll be surprised
bro what ends up happening as because we
all know where the market in in general
is heading right now you know
even as we see the dxy rise it's like
it's no [__]
uh you know question as to why it's
rising they stop printing money so it's
like they stop printing money what does
that do to our money increases the value
no different than [__] pokemon cards
or sports cards or cars itself you know
i own like they're up there i don't like
2 000 cards i have some serious cards
there but i like baseball cards baseball
pokemon just off a few that you have
maybe somebody watching this wants one
bro i have left off of you i have cars
there i have the um the full fleet of
michael jordan
yes seriously yeah i'll bring it right
here whoever wants to buy this [__] off
me please message me this is probably
the best bro but like so
the issue with this thing right here is
that you got to get them like verified
yeah you got to send them to um psoa
yeah tsa or psa whatever it is yeah so
they're like graded yeah you gotta give
them like uh
quality assurances
but i have cards in there like 40 years
old which is ridiculous yeah it's like
nft holding that type of forget that
but yeah to your point that's that's
where i was just like with the cryptos
i'm like you know what from this point
on forward anything that invests in the
crypto i'm trading like real estate so
let it do its thing and over time it'll
go up and value i hope i mean especially
now bro it's like it's obviously
it's just reverse order as far as how
you got in you know it's like everything
was at an all-time high you're seeing
arenas get bought up and labeled and
it's like that's crazy bro this is the
concept bro it's like it's like as you
see everyone else jumping on it's almost
to be expected like all right we gotta
take one more dip and that's why we keep
telling people zoom out like zoom the
[__] out like go to the daily go to the
weekly go to the monthly and you'll
still see for the majority that these
are still all bullish patterns it's like
but that's where you can tell when
people are putting more in than what's
actually risk capital and it's like i
get it we all do that but like
the self acknowledgement of i'm only
tripping over this bread being in
drawdown because i put in way more than
i would associate before yeah people
really need to know the difference
between being an investor and a
speculator an investor when your
investment goes down you have
a conviction in it so you just keep
putting more and more into the
investment the speculator when their
investment goes down starts to panic
because you don't believe in that [__]
in the first place so if you actually
believed in what you were buying in the
first place as it dips down you see a
discount as an investor a speculator
starts to panic as soon as they're on
drawdown so if you don't believe in what
you're buying this isn't you know it's
not financial advice but now is the time
to dump that [__] because over the next
12 to 18 months only quality assets
survive so
basically you mentioned you want to get
into real estate if you want to disclose
or because you're very educated like
there's some [__] you say where i'm like
what the [__] you know so what what why
are you getting into real estate you
don't think it's going to drop first
things first if a multi-family expert is
watching this if you guys are a real
estate agent in miami i'm looking for
multi-family use eight units preferably
somewhere close to the hot spots but
fire really uh real estate
is two parts one it's a chance for you
to
own a piece of land and to be able to
develop it and add value to it so people
there you see a specific property you
can actually improve the quality of
living there just off basic stuff some
people don't have a decent driveway some
people don't have decent air
conditioning need renovations and air
conditioning living quality flooring
things like that so anywhere you can add
value i feel like that's where people
should be putting their attention really
it's also a great cash flow stream and
it's a great tax investment too so you
don't think it's going to retrace
anytime soon not in miami no no in the
rest of the country yeah q4 q1 you can
expect some kind of retracement in the
real estate market but specifically in
miami i feel like it's resistant that's
when you say i was i was playing poker
with the tpt guys with neo and uh sean
where's my invite bro
he beat me a chest he beat me in a pool
but i was scared he's scared for
you know yeah we there's gonna be
another fx summit you guys we're gonna
do fx summit 2023. if you guys didn't
see it
again
we're hosting another summit fx summit
2023 if you guys don't know we hosted a
summit back in may in 2022 here at the
miami beach convention center for
traders investors and crypto experts we
ended up doing a car show full dinner uh
vip events conferences uh trade show
everything in between next year we're
going to take it up a notch we're going
to do a double 07 type
you know themed event there might be
some water some boats and
i'm gonna leave it as a surprise
and one of the top two crypto exchanges
will be sponsoring the next event so
it's gonna be pretty big interesting
yeah i i know this last one was like it
was it was definitely an experiment it
was a learning curve let me get you guys
his take let me get the honest take here
alex got something to get off his chest
no i i i don't have another i think it
was great everything went for me it was
just like i was more amazed at the fact
that you could put a song in the same
room like that to me was like holy [__]
this guy figured that out because to
even get all of us you know and just on
the zoom call you did that first once
you got us on the zoom call all right
this guy's on to something because
getting a song with zuma that's like
impossible getting real on a phone call
is impossible
you're getting real cue me anthony cute
like like it's it's just something else
right so once you actually like once we
went to the walk through the first day
like oh this guy's serious like if you
haven't had not been working on it for a
year right like if i'm like pretending
like if you haven't had that
um but no to me i i think it went great
i think eric generally went perfectly as
planned for me i i think it was great i
like saw it from the very start i was
talking to alex about it he was like yes
it could really be it could be something
like let me know how it works out i
remember getting started to build a
building yeah
i think you told me like one of the
first guys and then like you were
meeting
me yeah
in the old
yeah and then you're like no i'm
too place
thinking of doing this thing and i told
you i'm like look bro if you could get
q1
and row i think you'll get everybody
though and you're just [__]
snowballed after that i mean it makes
everyone watching this knows it makes
sense when everybody's collaborating
everybody's happy everybody wins
everybody's just in a great
place because it's just more value a lot
of the time as traders we tend to get
very focused on what we're doing
especially our trading and what we're
doing because we need to be focused and
keep our distractions but every once in
a while it's really important for us to
get together to show people like it's
bigger than it's bigger than us and you
know keep everybody involved so that's
what we try to do with the fx summit
next year obviously it's a bit of a you
know a pressure pull because we have ftx
and coinbase trying to sponsor so now
there's a certain standard we have to
reach but the same kind of energy we
brought to the first one we're going to
bring to the second one
the first time it was like i can't
believe i'm having a conversation with
alex i can't believe i'm talking to
jason on the side of this thing and he
gave me this one piece of insight that
changed my life
that sort of thing we want to keep
bringing every year that's what we're
going to be doing i think next should be
like two three x no because everybody
thought it was legit a lot of people
were still speculated about it so i
think it'll be at least two three x way
more way more
like the first one's always the hardest
you know man like i remember when roy
came to me with the idea and just like i
could see the vision but once
once again me seeing the vision is not
the same as roy and his team and all the
people that were a part of it because
obviously you know roy had the vision
but there's a lot of people you know we
always talk about staying on the
shoulders of giants and it's like you
guys see us doing well but you don't see
everyone that's behind us supporting us
and helping us make moves it's like so
just to hear from the beginning and then
also see you know this man pull it off
with the team
it was you know it was a thing of beauty
because i was only there for the first
uh the first day and then i had to leave
and then i came back on that monday just
to celebrate the event but like
i mean
what can you explain to me like what
more can you ask for the first event the
pinnacle i kept talking about it being
the mecca because it's like
this niche is still so new bro
period like that those don't exist like
we're all like bro we're all we're all
under 40 bro like well most of them are
all under 35 like well alex is young bro
remind everybody at home
in general bro there was not many people
that was a part of the summit or spoke
or was you know i'm saying doing
something that's
under 30s honestly everybody was saying
130 or like early 30s training really is
a new game yeah people who grew up with
technology who grew up with the internet
those are the people who are gravitating
towards trading because really
like uh up until 2008 you have to call a
broker to put in a trade like 2008 oh
wow yeah like ecm brokers and electronic
control networks and metatrader none of
that really came out until the early
2000s so once that technology came out
it made it easy for people to trade
shout out to dr olson he made it
possible for people to take a micro lot
size and
open the door for everyone to start
trading
nowadays everybody can leverage as much
as they want trade however how much they
want you know the real key is
self-control and discipline yeah now you
have a blank ocean you have let's say an
x an x dollar amount in your account a
thousand dollars
you could blow the whole thousand
dollars in one trade you could leverage
it up to however you want the only thing
stopping you is your own self-discipline
so how do you guys think about this true
like the markets open ocean you can
leverage however much you want but you
have to create the parameters how do you
guys structure that yeah like i i it's
literally a free frog i think that's
probably like the biggest issue in
trading we know it's psychology i like
the structure but like if you don't have
structure in your own life as a whole
like if you're not organized you're not
educated you're not properly are you
saying like time blocks if you have no
organization in your life period whether
it's your job just anything you're not
it's not going to happen in the charts
because you just bring over that same
energy and it does it's not going to
make any sense you're going to be like
you're not going to be in in coordinate
with how you're supposed to be with the
market in my opinion and that's why i
feel like a lot of people fail because a
lot of people are just sloppy as they
are just regular you know they just go
about life you know children which is a
which is a cool way to live you get me a
lot of people are just fine with just
being just going by let's be honest no
no no let me stop this no no it's not
well if you're watching this and your
life is going by
cut that [__] out this is not a trial
run you have one chance yeah you are in
the game right now get the [__] out of
that chair you're vacuuming right now
you're doing your laundry get up and do
something this is not a trial run this
is not a drill well yeah you do only
have one letting life pass you by is not
okay you're gonna be 80 years old
but you're right in your life but but
there there's some other people that
they don't have like the same ambition
they're just cool with just making
whatever they make and they just rather
have a peaceful life you got me a lot of
people don't want to do that go the
extra mile to get the extra amount
that's basically what i mean yeah i mean
yeah yeah it's like it's important for
us to acknowledge that like in order for
the ecosystem of it all to drop like you
go to a starbucks and there has to be
somebody there to make the coffee and
give you the bagel or whatever you order
and like that's just the reality of it
so i learned a long time ago to not try
to force people into a lifestyle that i
believe
is called for me and that's where it's
like as long as people are searching
something that genuinely makes them
happy if it's a job that they genuinely
enjoy going to and they're happy to go
home to their family and their kids and
the dog and the fence and all that [__]
then they're winning like they don't
have to make 100k in a day like they're
[__] winning already so you know it's
like but if you are built like us then
it's
you know it's a difference in being a
dog here's the bowl of food every single
day it's going to be the same amount the
same [__] bowl the same water
versus the line you might not eat for
one day two days three days but like
when you do we're gonna take down
two big ass bison and like you know
we're gonna the whole the whole hood is
eating for the next couple hours believe
in yourself
put in the work
don't give up
ladies and gentlemen this is another
episode of the set and forget
broadcast we have three incredible
guests we have fx alex g qb stew the man
the myth the legend and of course roy jr
co-founder ceo tar addicts signing off i
appreciate you guys see you guys in the
next episode